Guide to the Ken Kennedy academic records, 1967-2007 MS 206
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Ken Kennedy academic records
1967-2007
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Kennedy, Ken
MS 206
66 Linear Feet (67 boxes)
31.9 Gigabytes Nearline access: MS0206aip_001 (31.9 GB)
This material reflects the multifaceted career of computer science pioneer Ken Kennedy, of Rice University. Ken Kennedy was the founder of Rice University's nationally ranked computer science program and one of the world's foremost experts on high-performance computing.
Biographical Sketch
Ken Kennedy attended Rice University, receiving a B.A. in mathematics (summa cum laude) in 1967. He pursued graduate studies at New York University, where he earned a M.S. in mathematics in 1969 and a Ph.D. in computer science in 1971. He returned to Rice University in 1971 to join the faculty of the Mathematical Sciences Department, rising to the rank of professor in 1980. He founded the Rice Computer Science Department in 1984 and served as its chair until 1988. He was named the Noah Harding Professor of Computer Science in 1985. In 1997, he became the first John and Ann Doerr Professor of Computational Engineering and, in 2002, he was promoted to University Professor. From 1997 to 1999, he served as Co-chair of the President's Information Technology Advisory Committee (PITAC).
Professor Kennedy founded the Rice Computer and Information Technology Institute in 1987 and served as its first chair. In 1989, he established the Center for Research on Parallel Computation (CRPC), a NSF Science and Technology Center, and directed it throughout its lifetime. He directed the NSF-supported Virtual Grid Application Development Software (VGrADS) Project, a collaborative seven-institution research effort focused on application development support for computational grids. He was also the project director of the academic partner contract for the Los Alamos Computer Science Institute (LACSI), which is headquartered at Los Alamos National Laboratory. He directed or co-directed four ongoing multi-institutional consortia: the Los Alamos Computer Science Institute (LACSI); the NSF-sponsored Virtual Grid Application Development System (VGrADS) project; the Gulf Coast Center for Computational Cancer Research (GC4R); and the Houston BioGrid consortium.
Kennedy's research interests included parallel computing in science and engineering, scientific programming environments, and optimization of compiled code. His last work fell into four main project areas: the Telescoping Languages Project; the Grid Application Development Programming Tools effort; research on Compilers and Tools for Scalable Scientific Computing; and the Massively Scalar Compiler Project. He published two books and over two hundred technical articles on programming support software for high-performance computer systems. Over his career, he supervised thirty-eight Ph.D. dissertations and he directed the construction of several substantial software systems for programming parallel computers, including an automatic vectorizer for Fortran 77, an integrated scientific programming environment, compilers for Fortran 90 and High Performance Fortran, and a compilation system for domain languages based on Matlab.
Professor Kennedy was elected to the National Academy of Engineering in 1990. He was named a Fellow of the AAAS in 1994 and of the ACM and IEEE in 1995. In 2005, he was elected to the American Academy of Arts and Sciences. In recognition of his achievements in compilation for high performance computer systems, he was honored as the recipient of the 1995 W. W. McDowell Award, the highest research award of the IEEE Computer Society. In 1999, he was named recipient of the ACM SIGPLAN Programming Languages Achievement Award, the third time this award was given.
Professor Kennedy's service to the national community includes time as member (1997-2001) and co-chair (1997-99) of the President's Information Technology Advisory Committee (PITAC). For his leadership in producing the PITAC report, "Information Technology Research: Investing in Our Future," he received the Computing Research Association Distinguished Service Award (1999) and the RCI Seymour Cray HPCC Industry Recognition Award (1999).
Kennedy regularly taught two courses in the Computer Science Department: Computer Science 515 (Advanced Compilation for High Performance Computers) and Computer Science 412 (Compiler Construction). Kennedy also originated Computer Science 314 (Applied Algorithms and Data Structures) and taught it for several years.
Ken Kennedy died after a long battle with cancer, Feb. 7, 2007. "Rice has lost one of its great intellectual leaders and a great human being," Rice President David Leebron said. "Ken Kennedy early on realized the power of computers to address real problems that confront people and the Earth. He leaves a great legacy for Rice and for mankind."
Excerpted from Ken Kennedy home page at Rice University, http://www.cs.rice.edu/~ken/ and news feature http://engr.rice.edu/newsletter/spring07/storypages/feature_story05.html, accessed Feb. 2, 2009.
Scope and Contents
This material reflects the multifacted career of computer science pioneer Ken Kennedy, of Rice University. It includes correspondence, notes, reports, research materials, drafts of papers and presentations, meeting minutes, publications, appointment books, awards and more. The materials document Kennedy's work with various centers such as Center for Research on Parallel Computing, committees he served on, the Rice Computational Science Depart, his teaching career, research, publications and awards.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Acquisition Information
This material was transferred from the office of Ken Kennedy in 2007 and 2008.
Arrangement note
Upon arrival, this material was in various states of order. It has been arranged into the following broad groupings, but has not been refined within those groupings. Researchers should emply keyword searching across the entire finding aid for particular topics.
Missing Title
Series I: Centers, 1988-2007 (Boxes 1-16)
Subseries A: CRPC, 1988-1999
Subseries B: HiPerSoft, 1998-2007
Subseries C: Gulf Coast Center for Computational Research (GC4R), 2002-2006
Series II: Committees, 1986-2007 (Boxes 17-39)
Subseries A: Rice University, 1986-2007
Subseries B: Non-Rice, 1987-2007
Series III: Rice Computational Science Department, 1981-2007 (Boxes 39-41)
Series IV: Teaching Career, 1973-2006 (Boxes 42-44)
Series V: Research, 1967-2003 (Boxes 45-52)
Subseries A: Research binders and notebooks, 1967-2000
Subseries B: Research files and notes, 1980-2003
Series VI: Academic papers, presentations, books and slides, 1971-2006 (Boxes 52-60)
Series VII: Personal/awards, 1970-2007 (Boxes 60-65)
Series VIII: Audio-Visual media, 1991-1997 (Box 66)
Series IX: Centers, addendum (Boxes 66-67)
Series X: Ken Kennedy, bios, memorials (Box 67)
Series XI: Laptop, 2007
Series XII: Digital Content
Index Terms
Subjects
Computer programming; Universities and colleges
Document Types
reports; corrrespondence; awards; publications; appointment books; notes
Subjects (Persons)
Kennedy, Ken
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University. Department of Computational Science; President's Information Technology Advisory Committee; Center for Research on Parallel Computation; Gulf Coast Center for Computational Cancer Research
- Series I: Centers, 1988-2007 (Boxes 1-16)
  - Subseries A: Center for Research on Parallel Computation (CRPC), 1988-1999
    - CPRC NSF Renewal Site Visit. 1991 Sept. 24-25. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - E-mail from Linda Torczon regarding "Action Items from CRPC Executive Committee Meeting." 1994 November 16. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Girl Games - Being U. 1995. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - CRPC GirlTECH 1995: "A Teacher Training and Support Program Addressing Gender Issues and Technology" Proposal. 1995 February 10. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - CRPC NSF 3 Year "GirlTECH: A Teacher Training and Student Council Program Proposal." March 1996. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - CRPC GirlTECH 1997 Preliminary Proposal. 1996 May 15. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Knowledge Transfer Through the National Science and Technology Centers" 1993. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - CRPC Interim Site Visit Schedule and Materials. 1993 September 9-10. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - CITI/CRPC 1993 Calendar of Events (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1NSF Site Visit Reports Sept. 8-10, 1993. 1993 October 25. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - CRPC National High Performance Software Exchange (NHSE) Site Visit. Agenda and materials. 1996 December 4. (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - CRPC National High Performance Software Exchange (NHSE) Site Visit. Agenda and materials. 1996 December 4. (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - NSF Proposal: A Student Conference on Computational Science and Engineering for Minority Institutions in the South-Central United States. 1995 March 14. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - NSF Science Technology Center Meeting. 1994 October 31-November 1. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - NSF STC Center Directors' Meeting. 1996 July 29-30. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - CRPC Site Visit Handbook. 1988 July 6-7. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Proposal to the Office of Science and Technology Centers Development, NSF: Center for Scientific Parallel Programming. 1988 January 15. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Director's Narrative of Science Technology Center Annual Report. 1991 February 6. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Department of Health and Human Services Proposal: BCM Human Genome Program Center. 1990 February 1. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - NASA Proposal: A National Software Exchange for the High Performance Computing and Communications Program. 1994 September 4. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - CRPC External Relations Transition Plan. 1998 November 15. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - CRPC Corporate Sponsor Letters for Annual Meeting. 1997. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Pictures of Center Site Visit Participants. 1988 July 6-7. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Department of Energy Proposal: Electronic Studios for Distributed Organizations. 1992 October 23. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Scalable I/O Proposal Drafting Meeting. 1993 August 11-12. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - NSF Proposal - Parasol: A Laboratory for Parallel Software Technology. 1986 September 11. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - CRPC Research and Administrative Plan. 1990 February 14. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - NSF Proposal: National Computational Science Alliance (NCSA) Partnerships for Advanced Computing Infrastructure (PACI). 1997 August 13. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Scalable I/O Proposal. 1993 August 2. (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Subcontract between University of California San Diego regarding NSF Project "National Partnership for Advanced Computational Infrastructure (NPACI)." 1998 January 20. (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - NSF Proposal: Support for Innovative Applications of High Performance Computing in Houston. 1196 May 15. (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - CRPC Commitment of Support for Office of Naval Research proposal "Transport Rollback Recovery in Large Distributed Systems." 1990 April 30. (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Subaward Agreement between the University of Illinois and Rice University regarding NSF Cooperative Agreement. 1998 February 4. (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - NSF Proposal: National Computational Science Alliance - Empowering Computational Science, Engineering, and Education through Partnerships for an Advanced Computational Infrastructure. 1996 September 3. (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - CRPC Directory of Students with Experience with CRPC Resources. 1994. (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - CRPC Corporate Affiliates All Programs. 1995 July 26. (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Subrecipient Agreement between Syracuse University and Rice University regarding Cooperative Agreement No. CCR-9120008. 1995 June 28. (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - An Education Plan for CRPC, draft O.2. 1993 February 17. (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - NCSA Alliance Site Review Rough Agenda. 1996 October 28-30. (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Scalable Computing Workshop Agenda and Notes. 1993 October 18-22. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - NSF Proposal: Early Access and Evaluation of Scalable Distributed Share Memory Architectures. 1995 June 6. (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - The Ohio State University Letter to Ken Kennedy regarding the National Center for Computational Atmoic and Molecular Physics Proposal. 1992 November 4. (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - CRPC Newsletter - Parallel Computing Research. 1994. (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - CRPC Newsletter - Parallel Computing Research. 1993. (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - CRPC Renewal Site Visit. 31 August - September 2, 1994 (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - CRPC Renewal Site Visit. 31 August - September 2, 1994 (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - CRPC Grand Challenge Outreach Consortium, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Timeline for Science Technology Center Brochure. 15 November 1994. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - CRPC Interim Site Visit Notes. August 1993. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - South-Central Computational Science in Minority Institutions Consortium (SC-Cosmic) Conference Funding Final Report. 1995. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - National Institutes of Health Proposal: A Software Environment to Support Large-Scale Sequencing. 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - CRPC Parallel Computing Handbook Reviews. 2001. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Pablo System Proposal Notes, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - MDO Course Proposal. 12 February 1993. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - NSF MDO Grand Challenge. 12 March 1993. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - John Dennis - MDO Proposal. 21 May 1992. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - MDO - Boeina talk (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Nonlinear Programming (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Multidisciplinary Optimization. 7 May 1992. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - RI Proposal (Willy). 30 July 1996. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - RI Proposal Background. November 1991. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - NSF 91-78 REU Site (Tapia). 1 October 1991. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Mathematics (RUSMP). 17 March 1994. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - RI Site Visit. 20 January 1995. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - BAA 91-17 A Software Platform for Parallel Scientific Programming. 13 Dec 1991. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - ParaScope Data Partitioning. October 1990. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Wells Educational Proposal. 14 May 1992. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Texas ATP Proposal. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - CMX Proposal to NSF. 1992. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Subcontract between University of Tennessee and Rice University regarding cooperative agreement CCR-9120008. 14 June 1995. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - REU. 1992. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Texas Renewal Proposal, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Texas Renewal Proposal Drafts. 1995. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Holcombe SW Money. 1992-94. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - NASA Plan Report. July 1993. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - MADIC Drafts. January 1993. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - MADIC Meeting. 1992-93. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - NASA Query. 3 August 1992. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Grand Challenges with Scalable Supercomputers Draft Proposal. 27 January 1992. (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - MADIC/USMADE. November 1992. (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - CAS Project Task Plans - draft. 8 July 1993. (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - BAA 90-21 ParaScope Advanced Tools for Parallel Scientific Programming, copies/notes. 1990. (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - BAA 90-21 Notes for Syracuse/Rice Project. 1990. (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - CRPC Proposal Summary. (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Genesis Project Notes. (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - CRPC "Girl Games Prototype CD-ROM Project" Proposal. 27 September 1995. (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Technical Reports. 1989. (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Ron Parrot Proposal. (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Rome AFB Center. 12 August 1991. (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - R-Top Proposal Concurrent Control of Multiple Robots. 9 February 1990. (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Willy's Group Res Proposal. 1991. (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - CRPC Book/Tech Reports. (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - HPF-open MD meeting. 2000. (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - GirlTECH Notes (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Parallel Computing Research Newsletters. 1995-96. (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - CRPC Research, Education and Outreach Plan (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - SIO Conference Call. 6 February 1997. (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - SIO Conference Call. 4 June 1997. (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - SIO Conference Call. 22 April 1997. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - High Performance Fortran Forum. 30 January 1997. (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - High Performance Fortran Forum Letters. 1997. (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - HPF - Chinese Version. 28 May 1997. (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - HPFF. 24-26 February 1997. (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - 1990 Economic Summit at Rice University. (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Site Visit: Reviewer's Comments. 1994. (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - NSF: Sixth Year Renewal Proposals (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - NSF 3-year GirlTECH Proposal due September 1, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - NSF Review Response to 1994 Site Visit (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - CRPC Renewal Proposal. 23 March 1994. (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 1994 Site Visit Reviews (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - CRPC Renewal Site Visit. 1994. (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - ISAT (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Tapia Minority Program (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - CRPC Brochure and Lists (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - CRPC Plan (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Revision of CRPC Plan 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - CRPC Meeting Notes. 15-16 October 1990. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - CRPC Exec Comm. 28 June 1990. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - GirlTECH (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - EAC Briefing 1995. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - NAPA Research (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - NAPA Management (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - CRPC EC Overview 1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - CRPC Future (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - CRPC Plans (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - CRPC Affiliates (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - STC Directors Meeting. 17 November 1990. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Letter from Anita on the Center Annual Meeting (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Wallach Letter (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - CRPC Budget (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Annual CRPC Report 1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - CRPC Reviews (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Site Review Notes (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Rice/CalTech Center (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Renewal Site Visit (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Center Mode (Renewal) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Standards for Site Visit (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - CRPC Applications (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - CRPC Education Proposal (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - EC Video Conference (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - NSF Renewal Proposal. 1992. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - CRPC Education Plan (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - STC Plan: Center for Research on Parallel Processing. 1990. (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - EAC/IOC. 1995-96. (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - CRPC Directory (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - CRPC Directory (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Engineering Planning Meeting. 10 July 1996. (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - CRPC Report to Jennings. 1990. (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - CRPC Handbook. 1999. (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Koelbel Presentation (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - "Dependence Analysis for Subscripted Variables and its Application to Program Transformations" Thesis by John Allen. 1983. (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - CRPC Book Meeting. 29 June 1999. (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - CRPC Workshop. 1995. (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Institutional Oversight Committee (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Ken's Reply to Kieburtz Query; Attachment to Ken's Reply (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - PFC Listings Notes (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - John Wooley Notes (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - CRPC CalTech Meeting (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - EAC Meeting Notes (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - CRPC Executive Committee Notes. January 1993. (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - CRPC Add-On (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - CSCC Archive and Parallel Resources Interface Proposal (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Craig Fields Initiative (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - CRI/ CRPC Collaborative Proposal Draft (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Proposal notes/articles (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Status Worksheet (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - CASA Proposal (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - CAS Project Amendment No. 1 and questions/answers (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - CAS Systems Software (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Education - NSF Proposal notes (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Dependence project notes (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Computer Science Compilation Masters Notes (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Army Center Proposal Notes (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Amendment 0003 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Final Budget October 14, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Superb Tape University of Vienna (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Special Issue of Concurrency, Practice and Experience notes (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Senate Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - INR Tape UT-Austin (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - CRPC /VNS Meeting. 21 April 1992. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Minority Retention Proposal (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Gorry Training Grant (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Keck Graduate Research Traineeship Program Proposal (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - MPP Vision (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - MPP Proposal (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - UH Proposal (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - UH Proposal Background (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Maui SC Center Proposal (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Army Site Visit (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - NSF Center Budget Activities. 1989. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Centers/Institutes Directors' Meetings. 19 July 1996. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - CAPS Proposal: Renewal ATM88-09862. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - STC Site Visit. 2001. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - VNS (Gorry) Proposal (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Allen/Kennedy Book. 1991-92. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - NSF STC's Research Strategies in Research Centers. 2002. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Compaq-Rice Research Collaboration. 1998. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Compaq External Technology Program. November 1998. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Compaq Meeting. 15 April 1998. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Compaq-Rice Research Project (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - CRPC Renewal 1991 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Survey of Directors of NSF Sponsored STCs. 1995. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - STC Directors Notes (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Baylor Site Visit. 22 June 1990. (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Improving Research and Undergraduate Education in Computer Science Site Visit. 25 May 2005. (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - CE Bldg. Lecture (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Subcontract between Rice University and CalTech. CCR-9120008. 30 May 1995. (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Subcontract between Rice University and CalTech. CCR-9120008. 9 July 1996. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Senators' Letters (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Site Visit 1993 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - EC Video/Tele Conference. 5 September 1995. (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - EC Video Conference. 2 July 1996. (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - EC Video Conference. 26 January 1995. (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Letters of Support. 1994. (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Site Visit Bibliography (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Slides (Site 1994) (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Books - 94 Site (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Reviewers' Responses (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Books (1994 Site Visit) (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Student Letters (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Site Visit Schedule (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Annual 1994 Bibliography (re-format) (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - 1994 Originals Reviews (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Renewal (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - 1994 Site Visit (General) (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - 1995 Pubs Annual Report (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - 1995 Site Visit (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - 1995 Annual Report (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Support - Renewal Letters (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - 1994 Thank you (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Reviews (Responses and Comments) (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - 1994 Site Visit Reviews (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - 1994 Site Visit (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - 1994 Report Example (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - 1994 Student Support Letters (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - EAC Recruiting 1995 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Rotation and List Policy (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - External Advisory Committee (Box 5, Folder 1)